

PROFILE SUMMARY:

Software developer passionate for share knowledge and transmit ideas, with more than two years of experience in customer service and software technical support. Interested in understanding how people consume digital products that we find in our environment and keen to create products through technology

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Phone: (+57) 3184639094 Email: juanllano93@gmail.com Website: https://juanse.tech/ Github: github.com/juansedev/ LinkedIn: @juansebastianllanogallego

TECHNICAL SKILLS

-JavaScript -React
-CSS -HTML
-MySQL -PostgreSQL
-Git -C

-Data structures & -Python algorithm -Linux

SOFT SKILLS LANGUAGES

-Leadership -Spanish (Native) -Empathy -English (A2)

-Teamwork -Adaptability

PROJECTS

 Developer portfolio: Developer portfolio, in this project a SPA is created using React-router-dom, React-reveal, HTML, and CSS.

Website: https://juanse.tech

Github repository

 Hovify:Holberton portfolio project. Website Implemented using HTML, CSS, React, React-router-dom, React-reveal, React-hook-form, Material-UI, and RESTful API.

Website: https://hovify.works/

Github repository

- AirBnB Clone:Implement a clone of AirBnB website, using Html, CSS, JavaScript, MySql, RESTful API and Python. Website: https://juansedev.github.io/Github repository.

JUAN SEBASTIAN LLANO GALLEGO

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE:

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - REACT

Portfolio project - HoviFy | September- October 2020

Participation in the creation of the prototype, development, and, implementation of the front of a web application with React, React router, React hook form, Fetch, CSS Grid, CSS Flex, and Material-UI.

About the project, it is an application that allows you to create a curriculum vitae with the information from your LinkedIn profile. <u>Landing page</u> and <u>Github repo</u>

IMPLEMENTATION LEADER / ELECTRONIC BILLING SUPPORT.

QualityColombia S.A. | March - December 2019

- Manage the development of new functionalities and bug fixes at the level of electronic billing software
- Documentation of bugs and generation of test scenarios for developments.
- Assignment of projects to implementation consultants.

SOFTWARE SUPPORT CONSULTANT

QualityColombia S.A. | June 2018 - December 2019

- Installation of an application server for Java Web project on Linux and Windows servers.
- Software update at the application level and SQL database.
- Third level support electronic billing projects.
- Implementation of the electronic billing software.
- Training and orientation on the use of the services offered by the company to end customers.

Other work experience items via Linkedin

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Holberton School

February - October 2020

TECHNOLOGICAL SPECIALIZATION QUALITY METHODOLOGIES FOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 2019

ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGIST

Universidad del Valle 2011 - 2014



PROFILE SUMMARY:

Software developer passionate for share knowledge and transmit ideas, with more than two years of experience in customer service and software technical support. Interested in understanding how people consume digital products that we find in our environment and keen to create products through technology

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Phone: (+57) 3184639094 Email: juanllano93@gmail.com Website: http://juanse.tech/ Github: github.com/llanojs/

LinkedIn: @juansebastianllanogallego/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

-JavaScript -React
-CSS -Html
-MySql -Postgres
-Git -C
-Data structures & -Python
algorithm -Linux

SOFT SKILLS LANGUAGES

-Leadership -Spanish (Native) -Empathy -English (A2) -Teamwork

-Adaptability

PROJECTS

 - AirBnB Clone:Implement a clone of AirBnB website, using Html, CSS, JavaScript, MySql, RESTful API and Python.
 Static website: https://llanojs.github.io/
 Github repository.

JUAN SEBASTIAN LLANO GALLEGO

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE:

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - REACT

Portfolio project - HoviFy | September- October 2020

Participation in the creation of the prototype, development, and, implementation of the front of a web application with React, React router, React hook form, Fetch, CSS Grid, CSS Flex, and Material-UI.

About the project, it is an application that allows you to create a curriculum vitae with the information from your LinkedIn profile. <u>Lading page</u> and <u>Github repo</u>

IMPLEMENTATION LEADER / ELECTRONIC BILLING SUPPORT.

QualityColombia S.A. | March - December 2019

- Manage the development of new functionalities and bug fixes at the level of electronic billing software
- .- Documentation of bugs and generation of test scenarios for developments.
- Assignment of projects to implementation consultants.

SOFTWARE SUPPORT CONSULTANT

QualityColombia S.A. | June 2018 - December 2019

- Installation of an application server for JAVA Web project on Linux and Windows servers.
- Software update at the application level and SQL database.
- Third level support electronic billing projects.
- Implementation of the electronic billing software.
- Training and orientation on the use of the services offered by the company to end customers.

Other work experience items via Linkedin

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Holberton School

Febrary - October 2020

TECHNOLOGICAL SPECIALIZATION QUALITY METHODOLOGIES FOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 2019

ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGIST

Universidad del Valle 2011 - 2014



Juan Sebastian Llano Gallego

Software developer passionate for share knowledge and transmit ideas, with more than two years of experience in customer service and software technical support. Interested in understanding how people consume digital products that we find in our environment and keen to create products through technology

Get in touch!

Mobile: (+57)318 463 90 94

Email: juallano93@gmail.com

Website: http://juanse.tech/

GitHub: github.com/llanojs/

Twitter: https://twitter.com/llanoJS

LinkedIn: @juansebastianllanogallego/

Languages

English

- Reading: Intermediate
- Writing: Intermediate
- Listening: A2
- Speaking: A2

Spanish (Native)

Soft skills

- Leadership
- Empathy
- Workteam
- -Adaptability

Dev skills

-JavaScript -React -CSS -Html -MySql -Postgres -Git -C

-Data structures & -Python algorithm -Linux

Work Experience

Frontend Developer - react

Portfolio project - HoviFy | September - October 2020

Development of web application and landing page, participated in the prototyping, development and implementation of the web application.

About the project, it is an application that allows you to create a curriculum vitae with the information from your LinkedIn profile. <u>Lading page</u>

Implementation Leader / Electronic Billing Support.

QualityColombia S.A. | March - December 2019

- Manage the development of new functionalities and bug fixes at the level of electronic billing software
- .- Documentation of bugs and generation of test scenarios for developments.
- Assignment of projects to implementation consultants.

Software Support Consultant

QualityColombia S.A. | June 2018 - December 2019

- Installation of an application server for JAVA Web project on Linux and Windows servers.
- Software update at the application level and SQL database.
- Third level support electronic billing projects.
- Implementation of the electronic billing software.
- Training and orientation on the use of the services offered by the company to end customers.

Other work experience items via Linkedin

Academic History

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Holberton School

January - October 2020.

Technological Specialization Quality Methodologies for Software Development

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA)

2019. Graduate

Electronic Technologist

Universidad del Valle

2011 - 2014. Graduate



JUAN SEBASTIAN LLANO GALLEGO

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE SUMMARY:	WORK EXPERIENCE:
Software developer passionate for share knowledge and	FRONTEND DEVELOPER - REACT
transmit ideas, with more than two years of experience	Portfolio project - HoviFy September- October 2020
in customer service and software technical support.	Development of web application and landing page, participated in the prototyping,
Interested in understanding how people consume digital	development and implementation of the web application.
products that we find in our environment and keen to	About the project, it is an application that allows you to create a curriculum vitae with the
create products through technology	information from your LinkedIn profile. <u>Lading page</u>
CONTACT INFORMATION:	FRONTEND DEVELOPER - REACT
51 (57) 0104600004	Portfolio project - HoviFy September- October 2020
Phone: (+57) 3184639094	In this project its implement a clone of AirBnB website, using Html, CSS, JavaScript,
Email: juanllano93@gmail.com	MySql, RESTful API and Python.
Website: http://juanse.tech/	Static website: https://llanojs.github.io/
Github: github.com/llanojs/	Github repository: https://github.com/mfcrespo/AirBnB_clone_v4
LinkedIn:	
https://www.linkedin.com/in/juansebastianllanogallego/	IMPLEMENTATION LEADER / ELECTRONIC BILLING SUPPORT /
TECHNICAL SKILLS	SOFTWARE SUPPORT CONSULTANT
TECHNICAL SKILLS	QualityColombia S.A. June 2018 - December 2019
-JavaScript -React	- Manage the development of new functionalities and bug fixes at the level of electronic
-CSS -Html	billing software, documentation of bugs and generation of test scenarios for
-MySql -Postgres	developments. Third level support electronic billing projects.
-Git -C	- Assignment of projects to implementation consultants.
-Data structures & -Python	Installation of an application server for JAVA Web project on Linux and Windows servers, software update at the application level and SQL database.
algorithm -Linux	Implementation of the electronic billing software, training and orientation on the use of
	the services offered by the company to end customers.
SOFT SKILLS SOFT SKILLS	and odd index and a state of the state of th
Leadership	Other work experience items via Linkedin
- Emparry ip	Other Work Capations Rome the Entreeth
Fernativy	ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:
- Aaany Briky	
-Adaptability	FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER
	Holberton School
LANGUAGES	Febrary - October 2020
	Febrary - October 2020
-Spanish (Native)	TECHNOLOGICAL SPECIALIZATION QUALITY METHODOLOGIES FOR
-English (A2)	SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT
	Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA)
	2019
	ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGIST
	Universidad del Valle
	2011 - 2014
	2011 - 2014
	Other items of education via Linkedin
4	



JUAN SEBASTIAN LLANO GALLEGO

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE SUMMARY:

Software developer passionate for share knowledge and transmit ideas, with more than two years of experience in customer service and software technical support. Interested in understanding how people consume digital products that we find in our environment and keen to create products through technology

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Phone: (+57) 3184639094 Email: juanllano93@gmail.com Website: http://juanse.tech/ Github: github.com/juansedev/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/juansebastianllanogallego/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

-JavaScript -React
-CSS -Html
-MySql -Postgres
-Git -C
-Data structures & -Python
algorithm -Linux

SOFT SKILLS

- -Leadership
- -Empathy
- -Teamwork
- -Adaptability

LANGUAGES

- -Spanish (Native)
- -English (A2)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

FRONTEND DEVELOPER - REACT

Portfolio project - HoviFy | September- October 2020

- Development of web application and landing page, participated in the prototyping, development and implementation of the web application.
- About the project, it is an application that allows you to create a curriculum vitae with the information from your LinkedIn profile. <u>Lading page</u>

IMPLEMENTATION LEADER / ELECTRONIC BILLING SUPPORT.

QualityColombia S.A. | March - December 2019

- Manage the development of new functionalities and bug fixes at the level of electronic billing software
- .- Documentation of bugs and generation of test scenarios for developments.
- Assignment of projects to implementation consultants.

SOFTWARE SUPPORT CONSULTANT

QualityColombia S.A. | June 2018 - December 2019

- Installation of an application server for JAVA Web project on Linux and Windows servers.
- Software update at the application level and SQL database.
- Third level support electronic billing projects.
- Implementation of the electronic billing software.
- Training and orientation on the use of the services offered by the company to end customers.

Other work experience items via Linkedin

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Holberton School

Febrary - October 2020

TECHNOLOGICAL SPECIALIZATION QUALITY METHODOLOGIES FOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA) 2019

ELECTRONIC TECHNOLOGIST

Universidad del Valle 2011 - 2014